const gameData = [
    {
      question: "10",
      answer: "ten",
    },
    {
      question: "12",
      answer: "twelve",
    },
    {
      question: "1",
      answer: "one",
    },
    {
      question: "2",
      answer: "two",
    },
    {
      question: "3",
      answer: "three",
    },
    {
      question: "4",
      answer: "four",
    },
    {
      question: "5",
      answer: "five",
    },
    {
      question: "6",
      answer: "six",
    },
    {
      question: "7",
      answer: "seven",
    },
    {
      question: "8",
      answer: "eight",
    },
    {
      question: "9",
      answer: "nine",
    },
    {
      question: "0",
      answer: "zero",
    },
];

export default gameData